# **Chandler Tan**



# Salesforce Developer

Driven and motivated Salesforce Developer, more than willing to relocate, with experience working on projects individually and on a team. Passionate and hardworking with an inclination for meeting project deadlines. Interested in a contributing role with a company promoting best practices and offering opportunities to continue my learning.



# **Education & Training**

#### Salesforce Developer

Mar 2020 - May 2020

Salesforce & Deloitte Pathfinder Program - Indianapolis, IN

- Trailhead: 55+ badges, 44,000+ points, 6 trails, 1 Super badge Process Automation Specialist (Expeditioner Rank)
- Learned the technical and business soft skills necessary to pursue a career in the Salesforce ecosystem.
- Technical experience with the Salesforce platform, Apex, Visualforce, Lightning Web Components, and Unit

### **Software Development**

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

Eleven Fifty Academy - Fishers, IN

- Immersive development program covering HTML, CSS, C# and OOP fundamentals.
- Gained experience developing Console, Web, and MVC applications by myself, as well as in a team using various developer tools.
- Planned out Sprints on many projects to meet deadlines.

#### Earned Credits: Kinesiology and Exercise Science

Aug 2015 - Dec 2019

Indiana State University - Terre Haute, IN

Retail Associate – JC Penney

# **Work History**

#### Oct 2016 - Dec 2018

- Pursued resolutions to achieve complete customer satisfaction, including tracking down hard-to-find merchandise at diverse locations in order to maximize purchases.
- Maintained clean sales floor and straightened and faced merchandise, completing tasks 20% quicker than the average associate.
- Enhanced customer experiences by greeting customers in a timely fashion while also quickly determining their needs as well as providing product recommendations to increase sales.
- Provided customer service to 20+ customers daily.

#### Box Office Staff – Indianapolis Comic Con

May 2017 - May 2018

- · Managed efficient cash register operations, including scanning tickets off phones, processing payments and issuing receipts resulting in increased sales.
- Answered questions and concerns about event information to enhance the experience for the customers.
- Aided my fellow co-workers when needed to prevent burden on manager.
- Provided an effective transition from the opening and closing of event with a team in a timely manner.
- Provided customer service to 30+ customers daily.

#### Retail Associate – Toys R Us

May 2016 - Aug 2016

- Maintained accurate and attractive product displays, ensuring strategic placement of products in order to maximize purchases.
- Ensured optimal customer service by inquiring about experience and suggesting additional merchandise options to increase sales, ensuring that their needs and preferences were fully met.
- Worked at the 'Help Desk' to consult with customers and to provide answer to questions over the phone to further provide positive customer experiences.
- Provided customer service to 10+ customers daily.

Projects - (also available on my portfolio link)

#### BlueBox — ASP.NET MVC, completed alone

Created a movie/game rental application that utilizes .NET Framework MVC 5 Web Application using n-tier architecture. Tiers including data, models, services, and Web MVC.



### Contact

City

Indianapolis, IN

**Phone** 

(317) 993-7830

F-mail

tanchandler4@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/cha ndlert32/

**Portfolio** 

https://chandlert32.github.io/

Salesforce Trailblazer

https://trailblazer.me/id/ctan4



C# / HTML / CSS

.NET Framework

GitHub / Git

**VS** Code

Salesforce DX

Lightning Platform

Apex

Visualforce

**Developer Tools** 

Agile Development

**Unit Testing** 

SOQL / SOSL

Full-Stack experience



- Implements user roles, full CRUD on multiple tables.
- Configured the backend with C# and HTML & CSS on the front end.



#### Basic Db — database Web API, completed w/team of 4

- Developed a Web Application using n-tier architecture database using the C# language on the backend.
- Includes custom data tables, and utilizes foreign key relationships between tables. Also implemented REST.

## Hangman — console application, completed w/team of 2

Created a C# Console app based on the game 'Hangman' while incorporated pair-programming.
Deployed on GitHub.

### Web Store Front — HTML & CSS homepage, completed alone

• 'Pizza Planet' home webpage using HTML and CSS.

#### CSS Creature — CSS, completed alone

• Created a creature on code pen using only CSS.



Est. 2021

# **Certifications**

	· · · · · · · · · · · · · · · · · · ·
Nov 2020	Salesforce Platform Developer I
Apr 2020	Graduate Badge (Eleven Fifty Academy)
Apr 2020	Red Badge (3/3 Eleven Fifty Academy)
Mar 2020	Blue Badge (2/3 Eleven Fifty Academy)
Feb 2020	Gold Badge (1/3 Eleven Fifty Academy)

Salesforce Platform App Builder